question_data = [
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"]
		},
		{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
		 "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "True",
		 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
		{"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
		                                   "question": "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.",
		                                   "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
		{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
		 "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True",
		 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
		{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
		 "question": "In 'Overwatch,' an allied McCree will say 'Step right up' upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.",
		 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
		{"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
		 "question": "'Cube', 'Cube 2: Hypercube' and 'Cube Zero' were directed by the same person.",
		 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
		{"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
		 "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False",
		 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
		{"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
		 "question": "The Killer Whale is considered a type of dolphin.", "correct_answer": "True",
		 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
		{"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
		                                   "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
		                                   "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
		{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
		 "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
		 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
